[
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99E_MSQ_01_EnterEdengrove",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99E_MSQ_01_EnterEdengrove_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99E_Morgaine_p2v1",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99E_MSQ_01",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99D_MSQ_10",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99E_MSQ_01_EnterEdengrove_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "The Untamed Garden",
        "Description": "After a successful offensive in Great Cleave, the focus now turns to a more permanent solution for Corruption.\\nTravel into Edengrove with Sun and Morgaine to search for knowledge, weapons, or allies that may help in the battle ahead.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Why are you skeptical?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "The blight has only surfaced in recent years on Aeternum, while clashes between the Angry Earth and Corruption have occurred for centuries.\\n\\nMost don't even realize that the Stormwall is an expression of the Angry Earth.",
        "InProgressResponse": "UNUSED - WALKAWAY",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Good work in the ruins up there. If the Angry Earth were spawned after the first war with Corruption, they may well hold the secret to defeating it. \\n\\nI wonder if that's why Myrddin came to this region.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "EdengroveV2Arc1",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99E_MSQ_02_MyrddinClues",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99E_MSQ_02_MyrddinClues_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99E_Morgaine_p6",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99E_MSQ_02",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99E_MSQ_01",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99E_MSQ_02_MyrddinClues_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "On the Wizard's Trail",
        "Description": "Having reached the safety of the traveler's camp, Sun resolves to learn what she can before traveling to the settlement.\\n\\nAccompany Morgaine to the north in search of evidence of Myrddin's fate.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"I thought Myrddin fell to Corruption.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Eventually, yes, but he spent many years before that seeking answers about how he might study it, without falling under its influence.\\n\\nMy brother kept many secrets, and I believe some of them are hidden here in Edengrove.",
        "InProgressResponse": "UNUSED - WALKAWAY",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "There... his voice again, speaking as if he knew I'd come, and left some riddle… how? What games do you play, brother?\\n\\nTell me Soulwarden, what did you find in the sanctum that elicited this response?",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "EdengroveV2Arc2",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99E_MSQ_03_CollectSamples",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99E_MSQ_03_CollectSamples_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99E_Sun_p10",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99E_MSQ_03",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99E_MSQ_02",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99E_MSQ_03_CollectSamples_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "The Hope of New Growth",
        "Description": "While Morgaine remains in the Crystal Cave, Sun takes the opportunity to further explore the mysteries of the Angry Earth.\\nAccompany Sun on her exploration of the crater.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"What kind of sundering?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Myrddin was obsessed with the Ancients' methods of sundering the souls of their guardians.\\n\\nHe hoped it could allow him to study Corruption, protecting his soul from falling under its influence.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Meet with Sun and let her know what we have found. \\n\\nHer focus is on the Angry Earth, but mine is on my brother, as it should be.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Now, I think we've finally found something useful. The whispers spoke of the source, from where the Angry Earth's lifeforce is drawn.\\n\\nIf there is power to fight the Corruption, it is guarded within this Motherwell.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "EdengroveV2Arc1",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99E_MSQ_04_MotherwellClues",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99E_MSQ_04_MotherwellClues_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99E_Morgaine_p7",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99E_MSQ_04",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99E_MSQ_03",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99E_MSQ_04_MotherwellClues_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Dowsing for Answers",
        "Description": "Communing with the mind of the Angry Earth revealed a new facet of the strange creatures.\\nHelp Sun locate the sacred Angry Earth location called the Motherwell.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"So we follow the river's flow?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Ah, wait, but this is clearly not just the waters of this region, but rather the azoth that is undoubtedly bound to it.\\n\\nWe need some device with which we read the flow of azoth to triangulate the position of the Motherwell.",
        "InProgressResponse": "To think this could all be as simple as tracking the flow of azoth. Let us hope!",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Ah, Soulwarden, I've been waiting for your return! There is an incredible power hidden within the Ancient Towers here. \\n\\nAlmost everything in Myrddin's sanctum suggests he found something there… or left it for us to find.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "EdengroveV2Arc1",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99E_MSQ_05_UnlockPrison",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99E_MSQ_05_UnlockPrison_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99E_Galahad_p3a",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99E_MSQ_05",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99E_MSQ_04",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99E_MSQ_05_UnlockPrison_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "The Wizard's Trial",
        "Description": "Morgaine believes that Myrddin has hidden vital secrets away somewhere within Edengrove - and has a hunch that the towers around the crater may hold the key to finding them.\\n\\nTravel with her to the towers and investigate her theory.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"This could help us fight Corruption?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Precisely! My brother - fiendish bastard that he could be - was also a scholar of unrivaled insight.\\n\\nHe spent DECADES studying Corruption, and he hid his greatest discovery here… undoubtedly obscured by magical veils.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Myrddin definitely hinted that time was a critical component here, so let's not waste it.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "I can't believe it! That was not there a moment ago! That wizard floated a tower into the sky, then made it invisible!\\n\\nGod's teeth! Such powers should not be possible. I don't even know what to say.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "EdengroveV2Arc2",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99E_MSQ_06_MyrddinsPrison",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99E_MSQ_06_MyrddinsPrison_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99E_Sun_p6v2",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99E_MSQ_06",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99E_MSQ_05",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99E_MSQ_06_MyrddinsPrison_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Myrddin's Fate",
        "Description": "Unlocking the strange devices in the towers of Edengrove revealed a tower floating above the crater, which Morgaine believes to be Myrddin's prison.\\nInvestigate this strange area with Morgaine and Galahad.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"You don't have to come.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Every instinct screams that I should stay, but what kind of knight would balk at danger when so much is at stake?\\n\\nIf Myrddin is in there, I have questions, and he will answer or feel the sting of my blade!",
        "InProgressResponse": "UNUSED - WALKAWAY",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "It's about time! You were gone so long, I came to search and then I saw that floating tower appear in the sky! \\n\\nThis has something to do with Myrddin, doesn't it?",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "EdengroveV2Arc2",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99E_MSQ_07_RetrieveHeadpiece",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99E_MSQ_07_RetrieveHeadpiece_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99E_Sun_p14",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99E_MSQ_07",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99E_MSQ_06",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99E_MSQ_07_RetrieveHeadpiece_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "The Staff of Wizardry",
        "Description": "At Myrddin's urging, the hunt begins for the headpiece of his Staff of Wizardry, a relic that could shift the balance of power in the fight against Corruption.\\n\\nTravel to the southern mines of Edengrove and locate the headpiece of the Staff.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"It's buried in the mines to the south.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "That would be Annwn Deep... and that would explain the Corrupted massing that area! \\n\\nIf the Tempest already knows the staff's location, then there's not a moment to spare. You must go to Annwn and do whatever it takes to find it first.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Let me pack up here, I'll head out shortly. You have more than enough to deal with than to wait around for me.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "As usual, I find you walking away from a ruckus barely scathed. I thought my skills in healing might be of use, but I'm glad they're not.\\n\\nYou found the Corrupted Staff of Wizardry, did you? Yes, I sense it weighing on you.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "EdengroveV2Arc2",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99E_MSQ_08_AdianaPermission",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99E_MSQ_08_AdianaPermission_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99E_Sun_p15",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99E_MSQ_08",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99E_MSQ_07",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99E_MSQ_08_AdianaPermission_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Speaker for the Green",
        "Description": "With the headpiece of the Staff of Wizardry rescued from Isabella's forces, a way must be found to remove the taint of Corruption from the relic.\\n\\nFind the Speaker of the Green and gain permission to enter the Motherwell.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"We might be able to cleanse it.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Cleanse it? But what could possibly have the capability to cleanse such a powerful artifact? \\n\\nOh, well of course… you're probably thinking what I'm thinking. The Motherwell.",
        "InProgressResponse": "UNUSED - WALKAWAY",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "I only heard snippets that carried on the wind, but it was enough to know our request was not granted. \\n\\nMy mind is churning with backup plans, something, anything the elder druids might have written about.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "EdengroveV2Arc1",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99E_MSQ_09_TheMotherwell",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99E_MSQ_09_TheMotherwell_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99E_Morgaine_p2v2",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99E_MSQ_09",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99E_MSQ_08",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99E_MSQ_09_TheMotherwell_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "QuestReward_99E_MSQ_09_GuardiansSatchel",
        "ItemRewardQty": 1,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "The Motherwell",
        "Description": "Against Adiana's warning, the decision has been made to purify the Staff of Wizardry in the Motherwell… even knowing the consequences.\\n\\nEnter the Motherwell and purify the Headpiece of the Staff.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"That may be our only option.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Wait, are you seriously considering this? The Huntress warned that the staff would infect the Motherwell with Blight. I don't know how bad that may be, but would that be worth keeping the staff from the Tempest? \\n\\nStill, I can't say what's right here. I trust your judgment.",
        "InProgressResponse": "UNUSED - WALKAWAY",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Soulwarden? Are you here, or am I dreaming? I think I may have spent too much time at Myrddin's tower. Everything is… murky.\\n\\nTell me, were you able to get the Staff of Wizardry before the Tempest did?",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "EdengroveV2Arc3",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99E_MSQ_09_TheMotherwell_alt",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99E_MSQ_09_TheMotherwell_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99E_Morgaine_p2v2",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99E_MSQ_09",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99E_MSQ_08",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99E_MSQ_09_TheMotherwell_alt_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "QuestReward_99E_MSQ_09_GuardiansSatchel",
        "ItemRewardQty": 1,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "The Motherwell",
        "Description": "Against Adiana's warning, the decision has been made to purify the Staff of Wizardry in the Motherwell… even knowing the consequences.\\n\\nEnter the Motherwell and purify the Headpiece of the Staff.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"That may be our only option.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Wait, are you seriously considering this? The Huntress warned that the staff would infect the Motherwell with Blight. I don't know how bad that may be, but would that be worth keeping the staff from the Tempest? \\n\\nStill, I can't say what's right here. I trust your judgment.",
        "InProgressResponse": "UNUSED - WALKAWAY",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Soulwarden? Are you here, or am I dreaming? I think I may have spent too much time at Myrddin's tower. Everything is… murky.\\n\\nTell me, were you able to get the Staff of Wizardry before the Tempest did?",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "EdengroveV2Arc3",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99E_MSQ_10_ToCaerDun",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99E_MSQ_10_ToCaerDun_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99E_Yash_p3",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99E_MSQ_10",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99E_MSQ_09",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99E_MSQ_10_ToCaerDun_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "A Shadow Falls",
        "Description": "Morgaine's dream and Isabella's whispering tells of an attack on the Soulwarden fortress of Caer Dun.\\n\\nHurry to Caer Dun and investigate.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"I think it may actually have been attacked.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Really? Then what are you waiting for? You should go, before it is too late!\\n\\nI cannot see straight, let alone go into battle, but I will try and find you when I can. Make haste to Caer Dun, Soulwarden!",
        "InProgressResponse": "I will be fine. You should go to Caer Dun… as quickly as possible!",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "There you are! I've been watching so long my eyes are hurting.\\n\\nBut where is Yonas? Did you find him? I-I don't understand.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "EdengroveV2Arc3",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    }
]
